<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<menus>
  <menu name="mainroad">
    <prompt>
      You are on a road that heads East and West of your position.
      Which way will you go?
    </prompt>
    <choices>
      <choice link="spider">Go West</choice>
      <choice link="brickhouse">Go East</choice>
      <choice link="dragon">Wait for something to happen</choice>
    </choices>
  </menu>

  <menu name="spider">
    <prompt>
      You travel down the road, about only 100 metres and you encounter
      a giant spider with vicious poison coated fangs.
      its hideous appearance causes your throat to dry and your knees to shake!
      What on earth will you do?
    </prompt>
    <choices>
      <choice link="spiderattack">Attempt to attack the spider with your sword.</choice>
      <choice link="throwsword">Throw your sword in the off chance it might kill it.</choice>
      <choice link="running">RUN FOR YOUR LIFE!</choice>
    </choices>
  </menu>

  <menu name="spiderattack">
    <prompt>
      You viscously swing your sword at the spiders general direction.
      The swing was so great, your arms jolts out of place,
      creating a surge of pain.
      Your arm is now broken, and you fall to the ground in pain...
      The spider launches 3 metres straight into your body...
      What on earth is it doing?
      Oh My God! The spider is devouring everything...
      All that remained was bones of the once mobile adventurer.
    </prompt>
  </menu>
  
  <menu name="brickhouse">
    <prompt>
      You discover a brick house whose old front door is slightly ajar.
    </prompt>
    <choices>
      <choice link="mainroad">Go back the other way down the road.</choice>
      <choice link="brickhouse1">Go in.</choice>
      <choice link="house1_around">Wander around the house looking for another way in.</choice>
    </choices>
  </menu>

  <menu name="brickhouse1">
    <prompt>
      You enter the house.  An old lady is there and she offers you some soup.
    </prompt>
    <choices>
      <choice link="soup">Gratefully take the soup.</choice>
      <choice link="witch">Scream at the woman for being a witch.</choice>
      <choice link="mainroad">Leave and go back down the road the way you came.</choice>
    </choices>
  </menu>
  
  <menu name="dragon">
    <prompt>
      As you stand there in the middle of the road, eventually you notice a large bird circling overhead.
      Wait, no, it's not a bird.  It's a...  it's a....  DRAGON!!!
      You are roasted alive by a giant dragon.
    </prompt>
  </menu>

  <menu name="house1_around">
    <prompt>
      You wander around the house.  You step on a rusty nail.  It gets infected and you die.
    </prompt>
  </menu>
</menus>
